Due to limited computational resources in computer, I run 3 rounds instead of 6 rounds for generating best design. 

Small designs may already be optimized so We focus on large design: start from n = 15.

Then we only choose designs with nb. of columns >= 8 to see augmentation result for s-1,s-2,s-3...s-6 

TO control other irrelevant variables, we first use UDC("random") to generate best designs for 3 rounds and set maxiter=300*n for each n.

e.g.
    for design(n=27,s,q=3), maxiter=27*300 for all s. Then we use s-1,s-2,s-3,...s-6 to do augmentation search, Each of which is executed 3 
    rounds to select the best design. We record the result in Count_result.csv file.


Count_result.csv file:
    1-6 rows represent (s-1)~(s-6) correspondingly.
    7-th row represents the total designs we traverse.

Conclusion:
    在MD2条件下的Latin-Hyper cube实验，s-1列时比s-2,s-3,...s-6效果好。但是总体效果没有random generate好。
